A Guide to the Williams Family Papers, 1819-1993
Thomas Balch Library
- (OMB 2)
  - Artifacts
    - Artifact Tray 11
      - Tintype - unidentified boy, n.d.
      - Tintype - Ida Stone Winslow, n.d.
      - Tintype - Ida Stone Winslow, n.d.
      - Tintype - unidentified woman, n.d.
      - Tintype - unidentified woman, n.d.
      - Tintype - unidentified woman, n.d.
- (OMB 2)
  - Artifacts
    - Cover of Bible belonging to Edwin Winslow, obituaries glued to inside, n.d.
    - Helen Winslow Beskow's memoir, 1932 (family history), 1932
    - Notebook - genealogy notes, about Winslow family, n.d.
    - Book - Robert Williams of Roxbury, Mass., and His Descendents, by Edward H. Williams, Jr., 1891
    - Williams Genealogy (book), n.d.
    - Diary - Harrison Williams' third trip to Europe 5 October 1922-19 March 1923, 5 October 1922-19 March 1923
    - Helen Williams wedding book, n.d.
    - Notebook - poetry by Harrison William, 1883-1887
    - Pauline Williams wedding book, n.d.
    - Pauline Williams wedding memento book, n.d.
    - Eliza Pearce account book, 1857-1859
    - The Buffalo Club members book, James C. Harrison, 1873
    - Winslow Williams address book, n.d.
    - L'annee Poetique, 1890 - Pauline Williams, 1890
    - The Illustrated Shakespeare Birthday Book, to Gordon Williams from mother, 25 May 1887, 25 May 1887
    - Stereo slides (color) - 225 cards, 1954-1955